<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding the Reach: .it.com Domains Can Now Be Listed on the Dan.com Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://get.it.com/blog/expanding-the-reach-it-com-domains-can-now-be-listed-on-the-leading-domain-marketplace-dan-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>theitcomdomainsteam</dc:creator>
      <encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Today it.com Domains is pleased to announce that its domains are accepted for listingon Dan.com, a leading domain marketplace owned by GoDaddy. This expansion builds upon the initial <a href="https://get.it.com/blog/godaddy-now-offers-it-com-domains/">availability of .it.com domains through GoDaddy</a>, providing businesses and entrepreneurs with additional streamlined access to the .it.com domains through Dan.com's secure and user-friendly aftermarket domains platform.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Dan.com facilitates the buying, selling, and leasing of domain names, offering a seamless experience for users. Dan.com's importance in the domain market stems from its fresh approach to domain selling, focusing on transparency and ease of use. The platform's innovative features, such as instant domain transfers for certain ccTLDs and SEO-optimized landing pages, have made it a significant player in the secondary domain market.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The availability of it.com domains on Dan.com represents a significant opportunity for businesses of all kinds and industries to establish a strong online identity. With .it.com domains, companies can expand their options beyond traditional gTLDs, reach global markets, and enhance brand recognition within the IT community. Moreover, as .it.com domains operate within the established .com framework, they offer initial trust and seamless integration.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>By making .it.com domains accessible through multiple platforms, we enable more companies to foster innovation and success in the digital landscape. This collaboration with Dan.com complements the GoDaddy offering, creating even more opportunities for businesses seeking to thrive within the modern market space.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></encoded>
      <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
      <wp:post_id>1805</wp:post_id>
      <wp:post_date>2024-07-29 16:48:08</wp:post_date>
      <wp:post_date_gmt>2024-07-29 16:48:08</wp:post_date_gmt>
      <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
      <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
      <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
      <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
